<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>RepoBar</title>
        <item>
            <title>0.2.0</title>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/steipete/RepoBar/main/appcast.xml</link>
            <sparkle:version>4</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>0.2.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<ul><li>Fix the menu getting stuck on “Loading repositories…” by staging the initial repo list load.</li><li>Fix menubar clicks doing nothing by attaching the status item via a fallback path.</li><li>Add Personal Access Token authentication with persistence + logout fixes (#21, thanks @kkiermasz).</li><li>Add GitHub.com vs Enterprise login picker with OAuth help text (#4).</li><li>Show OAuth errors in Accounts sign-in UI (#6).</li><li>Add token status checks + forced refresh buttons in Settings for debugging auth issues.</li><li>Prevent token check/refresh from hanging; add timeouts and diagnostics logging.</li><li>Detect auth failures (401/refresh errors) and log out cleanly with a clearer message.</li><li>Preserve keychain access groups in signed builds so app + CLI share tokens (#16, thanks @jj3ny).</li><li>Allow importing GitHub CLI tokens with host matching and no refresh loop (#24, thanks @bahag-chaurasiak).</li><li>Surface a clear error when the OAuth loopback port is already in use (#17, thanks @kiranjd).</li><li>Add “Show only my repositories” toggle (owner filter) for repo lists and search.</li><li>Fix the toggle to reset to “show all” when disabled; disable it when signed out.</li><li>Fix commit links to respect GitHub Enterprise host (#9).</li><li>Make pinned/hidden repo matching case-insensitive (fixes private repo pinning edge cases).</li><li>Keep the menu open after pin/unpin/hide/move actions (#25, thanks @bahag-chaurasiak).</li><li>Make Local Projects scan depth configurable (default 4) (#11, thanks @shunkakinoki).</li><li>Stabilize repo settings autocomplete (no spinner layout wiggle), widen the dropdown, show repo stats/badges, fix filtering/hover/scroll, and anchor/size the dropdown to results (no bounce on shrink).</li><li>Widen Enterprise Base URL field and shrink auth progress indicators to avoid layout jumps.</li><li>Derive activity commit links from repo URL when event repo name is missing or malformed.</li><li>iOS: update app icon + logo assets.</li></ul>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/steipete/RepoBar/releases/download/v0.2.0/RepoBar-0.2.0.zip" length="15018239" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="qecsK4GJXXmRo7k1JNhRo/hdpqVmL7CWCJtAmZivihkL2IWpXorq3PQk/KE32FobhdKXdIweaZH+oLowVevlAw=="/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>0.1.2</title>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:40:17 +0100</pubDate>
            <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/steipete/RepoBar/main/appcast.xml</link>
            <sparkle:version>3</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>0.1.2</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<ul><li>iOS app preview (not finished, not in the App Store yet): repo list/cards, activity feed, detail drill‑downs, login/settings, icons/branding, and continued auth/UI polish.</li><li>CLI parity expansion: new repo list subcommands (releases, CI runs, discussions, tags, branches, contributors, commits, activity) plus `--owner/--mine` filters.</li><li>CLI local actions + settings: sync/rebase/reset/checkout, branch/worktree listings, Finder/Terminal open; pin/hide and settings show/set; installer for `repobar`.</li><li>Changelog UX: submenu preview improvements plus Markdown rendering upgrades (block layout, scrollable preview, header alignment).</li><li>Changelog UX: show the first released section headline in the submenu badge (skips Unreleased).</li><li>Changelog UX: prefetch on repo submenu open and refresh the badge after load.</li><li>Changelog UX: switch to Swift Markdown AST parsing for cross-platform block rendering.</li><li>Releases submenu: show latest release name next to the count badge.</li><li>Menu customization: Display settings to reorder/hide main menu and repo submenu items (reset to defaults), with spacing tweaks.</li><li>Logging/diagnostics: swift-log integration with OSLog + optional file logging; debug logging settings for macOS/iOS.</li><li>Reliability: menu rehydrate on attach, invalidate empty menu cache, stabilize contribution header heatmap size, limit “More” submenus to 20 entries.</li><li>Repo access + errors: include org/collaborator repos, improve repo detail error messaging, cache discussions capability and hide disabled entries.</li></ul>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/steipete/RepoBar/releases/download/v0.1.2/RepoBar-0.1.2.zip" length="14747018" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="CC6sk/wStzPOmGAaxiwo8f/JVJocglx5ZFtlZbNUor0d3tIVLqrlgrlsM0mWqBuVKkher5U3Bnu+L9EntzZ6Bw=="/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>0.1.1</title>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:08:30 +0100</pubDate>
            <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/steipete/RepoBar/main/appcast.xml</link>
            <sparkle:version>2</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>0.1.1</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<ul><li>Fix CLI: allow invoking bundled `repobarcli` directly (argv0 normalization).</li></ul>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/steipete/RepoBar/releases/download/v0.1.1/RepoBar-0.1.1.zip" length="11338886" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="nJ4XzYOz3dPYXdEXPJUnYCNJjdnR/j9l7yy5lgT7vxvr8yhe3e39B9Gh4Maf+Nqg5pNsL3xVPcCgbAraiXj9Ag=="/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>